amandapalmer.net 2018-12-19

# Privacy Policy The official website of Amanda Fucking Palmer. Yes it is - Amanda Palmer

Privacy Policy

This website is owned and operated by Amanda Palmer

What information do we collect?  
We may collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, land on a page with advertising targeting, respond to a survey or fill out a form. We may also collect information through a cookie for targeted advertising.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, birthdate, credit card information, or other personal information. 

What do we use your information for?  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:  
\- To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)  
\- To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)  
\- To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)  
\- To process transactions – Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.  
\- To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature  
\- To send periodic emails  
\- To advertise – The cookie we may install may be used for targeted advertising; the email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.  
How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

Do we use cookies?  
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. Cookies can also be used for targeted advertising.  
We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits, target and keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

Do we disclose any information to outside parties?  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

Third party links  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance  
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance  
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

Online Privacy Policy Only  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

Your Consent  
By using our site, you consent to this websites privacy policy.

Changes to our Privacy Policy  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.  
This policy was last modified on October 15,2013

This policy is powered by Free Privacy Policy and Rhino Support help desk software.
